Guide to the Stefan Brecht Papers MSS.355
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: Mabou Mines
  - Later years of Mabou Mines- [and "Dollhouse"], [undated] (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - "In the Jungle of Cities", [1991-1992] (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - "The Bribe"- [Terry O'Reilly], May, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - "The Quantum"- [A Life in the Gallery- Twenty Years of Mabou Mines], [December, 1990] (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Joann Akalaitis, [undated] (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - "An Epidog"- [annotated typescript in binder] [1 of 6], [undated] (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - "An Epidog"- [signed script] [2 of 6], [undated] (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - "An Epidog"- [3 of 6], [1997] (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - "An Epidog"- [International Festival of Pupper Theater with Lee Breuer correspondence] [4 of 6], [1996] (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - "An Epidog"- [includes "Mother" and "Reel to Real"][5 of 6], [undated] (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - "An Epidog" [Includes "Mahabharanta" and "The Bribe"] [6 of 6], [undated] (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - "Peter and Wendy" and "Happy Days", [1996] (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "Red Horse" and "B. Beaver", [undated] (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Dressed Like an Egg"- [Brecht's Notes], 1977 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - "Dressed Like an Egg" and "Shaggy Dog", 1977 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Adapting Beckett- ["Come and Go","Ohio Impromptu", "Catastrophe","What Where", "Westward Ho"], [undated] (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - "Cascando"- Beckett, April 8-May2, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Beckett at Theatre for the New City, March 7, 1975 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - "Red Horse" and "B. Beaver" [1 of 7], 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - "Big Deal 4" Fall, 1976 [Magazine with article on "B. Beaver" animation] [2 of 7], 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - "Dressed Like an Egg"- [3 of 7], 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - "B. Beaver" and "Red Horse" Animations [4 of 7], [1975-1978] (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Adapting Beckett- ["Come and Go", "Lost Ones", "Play"] [5 of 7], 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - "The Red Horse Animation" text by Lee Breuer, art by Elizabeth Hornton [limited edition comic book with note from Lee Breuer][6 of 7], 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - "The Saint and The Football Players" [7 of 7], 1975-1978 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - [Beckett Festival and The Obies clippings], [undated] (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Semiotexte III/2 [Sylvere Lotringer interviews Lee Breuer], 1978 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - "Southern Exposure", 1979 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - "Richard III" [Al Pacino], [undated] (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - [Letter to Dick Landry requesting photographs], March 22, 1979 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - [Fifth Annual Benefit for the Tibetan Center], June 1, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Ken Kobland- "Frame", "Picking up the Pieces", "Vestibule", "Near and Far/Now and Then", 1979 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Lee Breuer [Brecht's Notes on Breuer's Language], June 17, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - "A Prelude to Death in Venice", [undated] (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "Animations: A Trilogy for Mabou Mines: The Red Horse, The B. Beaver, The Shaggy Dog" [Book by Lee Breuer edited by Bonnie Marranca and Gautam Dasgupta], 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - [Articles on Animations and "Other Stages" Vol. 2 No. 3], [1979] (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - "A Piece of Monologue" [Samuel Beckett], 1979 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Naropa Institute- The Mudra Theater Group, August-September, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - "Mercier and Camier" [Samuel Beckett], 1979 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - "Dead End Kids" [Joanne Akalaitis], [undated] (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - "Sister Suzie Cinema"- [Lee Breuer and Bob Telson], 1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - "Sunday Childhood Journeys to Nobody at Home", [1980] (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - David Warrilow- [Press Releases and Articles], [1980] (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Doris Chase- "Lies" [and "The Red Beads"], [undated] (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - "Wrong Guys", [undated] (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - "Wrong Guys" [and "Other Stages" Vol. 4 No. 1], [1981] (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - "Wrong Guys" [Brecht's Notes] [1 of 4], May, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - "Wrong Guys" [Brecht's Notes] [2 of 4], May, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - "Wrong Guys" [Brecht's Notes] [3 of 4], May, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - "Wrong Guys" [Brecht's Notes] [4 of 4], May, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - "Ecco Porco", Spring, 2001 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "Ecco Porco", 2001, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - "Las Horas de Belen"- The Book of Hours [and "Animal Magnetism", 2000 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - "Animal Magnetism", 2000 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - "Lear" [1 of 2], [undated] (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - "Lear" [2 of 2], [undated] (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - "Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said" by Philip K. Dick, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - "Flow My Tears, The Policeman Said"- Bill Raymond, June-July, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - "The Warrior Ant", [1988] (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - "Green Card"- Joanne Akalaitis, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - "The Gospel at Colonus" [articles and clippings], [undated] (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - [Miscellanous Articles and Clippings], [undated] (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - "It's A Man's World"- Greg Merthen and David Schweizer, May-June, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - "A Prelude to Death in Venice"- Dance Theater Workshop, May 17, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - "Hajj"- Lee Breuer, May 16, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - "Help Wanted"- Franz Xaver Kroetz, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - "The Warrior Ant"- Lee Breuer and Bob Telson, Alice Tully Hall, June, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence- Mabou Mines, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - "Starcock", [1985] (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "Suenos" [Twenty Years of Mabou Mines], [undated] (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - "The Balcony"- Joanne Akalaitis, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - "Westward Ho"- Frederick Neumann, June, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - "Lear"- Lee Breuer, January-February, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - "The Screens"- Joanne Akalaitis, [1989] (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - [Mabou Mines' Twentieth Anniversary- "B. Beaver"], [May, 1990] (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - "Gospel at Colonus" [1 of 2], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - "Gospel at Colonus" [2 of 2], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - "The Photographer/ Far From the Truth"- [1 of 2], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - "The Photographer/ Far From the Truth"- [2 of 2], 1983 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Series IV: Performance Group "Wooster Group"
  This series comprises files compiled by Brecht in the course of his research for his unfinished book on the Performance Group "Wooster Group." The research documents the Performance Group under the direction of Richard Schechner as well as their evolution into The Wooster Group with works of Spalding Grey, Elizabeth LaCompte, and others. The series includes interviews with Richard Schechner and Joan MacIntosh. Research files on the Living Theater and Open Theater are included in this series; Brecht may have been making an intended connection between them. The series contains notes, newspaper clippings, original scripts, correspondence, and ephemera including posters, tickets, and invitations organized by production. Material ranges from 1960s to 2000s. Interview transcripts can be found of correlating audio material.
  - "Based on Bacchae"- Richard Schechner's files [1 of 3], 1960 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - "Based on Bacchae"- Richard Schechner's files [2 of 3], 1960 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - "Based on Bacchae"- Richard Schechner's files [3 of 3], 1960 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - "Choices: Making an Art of Everyday Life" by Marcia Tucker, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "Situations of Confrontation" at the Performing Garage, February 6-8, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Leo Robin, [undated] (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - "The Road to Immortality (Part Two)- L.S.D.", 1986 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - "The Road to Immortality (Part Three)- The Temptation of Saint Anthony", January, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - "The Road to Immortality (Part One)- Route 1 and 9", December 1986-January 1987 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - [Brecht's notes on race and anti-semitism], [undated] (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - "Platoon"- [articles], [1987] (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - "First Law of Attraction"- Jim Strahs, January 6, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - [Wooster Group Newspaper Clippings], [undated] (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - [Wooster Group Articles], [undated] (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - "Hoodwink"- Nancy Reilly [and "LSD"], January-February, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - "The Road to Immportality (Part III)- Frank Dell's St. Antony", April 25, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - "The Road to Immportality (Part III)- Frank Dell's St. Antony"- Invitation-only performance, November 28, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - "Our Town", [1988] (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Interview- Joan MacIntosh [Brecht's Notes], June 29, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Interview- Richard Schechner [Brecht's Notes], April 3, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Interview- Richard Schechner [Transcript], April 3, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Interview- Joan MacIntosh [Transcript], March 22, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Interview- Richard Schechner [Transcript], March 12, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - The "Free Southern Theatre", 1969 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - The "Free Southern Theatre"- [correspondence], 1986 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - The "Free Southern Theatre"- Richard Schechner and "The Prometheus Project", [1985-1986] (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - "The Prometheus Project"- Richard Schechner, December, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - "The Free Southern Theater by The Free Southern Theater" edited by Thomas C. Dent, Richard Schechner, and Gilbert Moses, 1969 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - "Back Bog Beast Bait"- Schechner directs Sam Shepard, December 6-23, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - "Cowboys No. 2"- Schechner directs Sam Shepard, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - "Killer's Head, Action"- Schechner directs Sam Shepard, [undated] (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Five Plays by Sam Shepard; Chicago, Icarus's Mother, Red Cross, Fourteen Hundred Thousand, Melodrama Play" [book published by Faber and Faber], 1967 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - "The Best of Off Off-Broadway" edited by Michael Smith [book published by E.P. Dutton & co.], 1969 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - "Sam Shepard: Mad Dog Blues & Other Plays" edited by Michael Feingold [book published by Winter House], 1972 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - "The Unseen Hand and Other Plays" by Sam Shepard [book published by The Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc.], 1972 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "La Turista: a play in two acts" by Sam Shepard with an introduction by Elizabeth Hardwick [book published by The Bobbs-Merrill Company, Inc. with La Turista materials from The American Palace Theater], 1968 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - "Operation Sidewinder: a play in two acts" by Sam Shepard [book published by The Bobbs-Merrill Co., Inc.], 1970 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "Performance 5" vol. 1 no. 5 [includes Sam Shepard's script for "The Tooth of Crime"], March/April, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - "House/Lights", February, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - "The Emperor Jones", February, 1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - "North Atlantic" [William DeFoe], [1999-2001] (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - "The Hairy Ape", [1997-2001] (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - "Fish Story Part I and Part II", [1983-1994] (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Ron Vawter [articles], [1992-1993] (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Marianne Weems- [book proposal], February 25, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Spalding Gray- "Morning, Noon, and Night", "Gray's Anatomy", "Monster in a Box", [undated] (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - "Brace Up!"- "Three Sisters", January, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Annie Sprinkle, February, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Spalding Gray [articles and clippings], [undated] (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - [Articles on the Wooster Group], 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - "Alice in Bed" [and Richard Schechner], [1991, undated] (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Olga's "House of Shame"- [letter from Something Weird Video], October, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Richard Schechner transcript of lecture at NYU- "Dionysus in '69 and '91", March 19, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - "First Love" [articles], 2001 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - "To You, The Birdie! (Phedre)" [1 of 3], 2002 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - "To You, The Birdie! (Phedre)" [typescript copyright 1993] [2 of 3], 2002 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - "To You, The Birdie! (Phedre)" [3 of 3], 2002 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - "To You, The Birdie! (Phedre)" [Brecht's notepad], 2002 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Performance Group [clippings and 'Other Stages' vol. 4 no. 9][1 of 8], 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Performance Group [articles][2 of 8], [1975-1981] (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Performance Group- "Three by Gray", "The Balcony", "Point Judith" [3 of 8], [1975-1982] (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Performance Group- "Three by Gray", "The Balcony", "Point Judith" [4 of 8], [undated] (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Performance Group- "Point Judith" [5 of 8], January, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Performance Group- "Point Judith" and "The Last Act: A Revival" [6 of 8], [undated] (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Performance Group- "The Last Act: A Revival" [7 of 8], March, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Performance Group- "Request Concert" [8 of 8], 1981 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - "Other Stages" vol. 3 no. 14, 1981 and "Other Stages" vol. 5 no. 12, 1983 [with clippings], [1981-1983] (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - "LSD (Part I)", January, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - "Route 1 and 9", November 1981-Summer 1982 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - "Thilm" by Lita Eliscu from EVO vol. 3 no. 52 [article], November 29, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - [Articles on "LSD" "Route 1 and 9" and "The Crucible"], 1985 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - "Miss Universal Happiness"- [Richard Foreman], May 15, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - "L.S.D." and "The Crucible"- [Arthur Miller dispute] [articles], [1983-1985] (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - "North Atlantic", January 20, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - "Swimming to Cambodia" [and "The Killing Fields"], December 1984-January 1985] (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - "Sex and Death to the Age of 14"- [Spalding Gray], April 20-May 26, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - "The Wooster Group: A Brief History"- Press Release, June, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - "Rumstick Road"- Spalding Gray, 1977-1979 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - "Nyatt School"- [Spalding Gray and Elizabeth LaCompte], 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - "Sakonnet Point", "Three Places in Rhode Island", "A Wing and A Prayer", 1975, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - "Oedipus", "Cops", 1977-1978 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - "Mother Courage"- Richard Schechner, January-June, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - "Tooth of Crime" revival and "The Marilyn Project", 1975-1976 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - The Living Theatre- "Revolution at the Brooklyn Academy of Music" [article by Stefan Brecht] [1 of 5], [undated] (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - The Living Theatre- [reperatory and articles] [2 of 5], [undated] (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - The Living Theatre- [letter from Julian Beck to Stefan Brecht] [3 of 5], September 12, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - The Living Theatre- "The Living Theatre at Chapel Hill, North Carolina, Spring of 1973" [4 of 5] (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - The Living Theatre- "Seven Meditations" [5 of 5], 1973 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - The Open Theatre- [Jerome Chaikin- "The Mutations Show"], [1973] (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - "Dionysus in 69, from Euripides' The Bacchae The Performance Group" [article by Stefan Brecht], Spring, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Richard Schechner- "The Tooth of Crime" [1 of 2], [1973] (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Richard Schechner- "The Tooth of Crime" [2 of 2], [1973] (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Performance Group and Michael McClure [1 of 2], October, 1973-January, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Performance Group and Michael McClure [with annotated typescript of "The Beard"] [2 of 2], October, 1973-January, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Andre Gregory's Manhattan Project- "Alice in Wonderland" and "Endgame", [1973] (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - "Grotowski's production of The Constant Prince" [article by Stefan Brecht], [undated] (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Series V: Dance, Black Theatre, Black Music
  This series comprises files compiled by Brecht during research for his unfinished books on dance, black theater and black music. Although Brecht may have envisioned this as two separate books within the larger opus, the material is slightly interwoven. The series consists of notes, newspaper clippings, correspondence, and ephemera including posters, tickets, and invitations. Material ranges from 1960-1979 with a significant portion of undated material.
  - Criticism Book: Meredith Monk, [undated] (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Criticism Book: Yvonne Rainer [1 of 4], [undated] (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Criticism Book: Yvonne Rainer [Brecht's notes on "This is the story of a woman who..."] [2 of 4], 1973 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Criticism Book: Yvonne Rainer [includes correspondence] [3 of 4], 1974, undated (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Criticism Book: Yvonne Rainer- "Avalanche" [4 of 4], Summer, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Criticism Book: Merce Cunningham- Notes on Events #65-68 [1 of 6], March, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Criticism Book: Merce Cunningham- Notes on Events #79-82 [2 of 6], May, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Criticism Book: Merce Cunningham- Index to notes on Events #65-68 and #79-82 [with additional notes] [3 of 6], [undated] (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Criticism Book: Merce Cunningham [4 of 6], [undated] (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Criticism Book: Merce Cunningham [5 of 6], [undated] (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Criticism Book: Merce Cunningham- ["Ballet Review" vol. 1 no. 4, ed. by Arlene Croce with an interview of Merce Cunningham] [6 of 6], 1966 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Meredith Monk [1 of 3], [undated] (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Meredith Monk [2 of 3], [1976-1979] (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Meredith Monk [3 of 3], [1974-1976] (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Black Theatre [1 of 2], [undated] (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Black Theatre ["Inacent Black and the Five Brothers"][2 of 2], [undated] (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Black Music- Cecil Taylor and Sun Ra [1 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Black Music- Jeanne Lee [2 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Black Music- [3 of 3], 1975-1976 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Black Theatre [1 of 3], [undated] (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Black Theatre [Includes "The New Yorker" June 16, 1973] [2 of 3] (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Black Theatre- [Amiri Baraka (Leroi Jones) "A Recent Killing"] [3 of 3], December 25, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Black Theatre/Black Music- Original New York Theater [1 of 2], 1968-1973 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Black Theatre/Black Music- Original New York Theater [2 of 2], 1968-1973 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Cecil Taylor, [1973-1975] (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Sun Ra- "Space is the Place", October, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Cunningham/Rainer/Monk- [1 of 3], 1973 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Cunningham/Rainer/Monk- [2 of 3], 1973 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Cunningham/Rainer/Monk- [3 of 3], 1973 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Series VI: Sound recordings
  This series contains audiocassettes, audio reels, and a 12" vinyl sound disc. All audio material contains corresponding transcripts that can be found by searching for transcripts specifically or by their similar titles.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - Stuart Sherman on the 11th Spectacle (The Erotic)- Interview by Stefan Brecht, February 22, 1979; ID: 355.0001 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0001, Box Shared Fales 132, Cd 355.0001_pt.1, Cd 355.0001_pt.2)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Duration: Unknown
    Original format: 1/4" audiocassette
    Currently unavailable until duplication occurs.
  - Stuart Sherman on the 11th Spectacle (The Erotic)- Interview by Stefan Brecht, February 22, 1979; ID: 355.0002 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0002, Box Shared Fales 132, Cd 355.0002_pt.1)
  - Stuart Sherman on the 11th Spectacle. Continues last interview. 1st Cassette of May 2nd.- Interview by Stefan Brecht, May 2, 1979; ID: 355.0004 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0003, Box Shared Fales 132, Cd 355.0003_pt.1, Cd 355.0003_pt.2)
  - Stuart Sherman on the 11th Spectacle. Second tape of May 2nd evening. Interview by Stefan Brecht, May 2, 1979; ID: 355.0004 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0004, Box Shared Fales 132, Cd 355.0004)
  - Stuart Sherman on Richard Foreman and notably "Sophia The Cliffs", February 24, 1986; ID: 355.0005 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0005)
  - Stuart Sherman on Richard Foreman (Second tape) and Stuart Sherman on "Verticle Mobility" and "Pain(t)", February 2, 1986; ID: 355.0006 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0006)
  - Stuart's "Portraits of Places" and "3 in One"- Interviews with Sarah, Mary, February 27, 1978; ID: 355.0007 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0007)
  - Stuart Sherman on the 11th Spectacle- Third Session. Second Tape of this evening., March 6, 1979; ID: 355.0008 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0008)
  - Stuart's "Portraits of Places", March 19, 1978; ID: 355.0009 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0009)
  - Stuart Sherman on the 11th Spectacle- Third Session begins here., March 6, 1979; ID: 355.0010 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0010)
    Currently Unavailable until duplication occurs.
  - Interview with Stuart Sherman on four movies of his- Part two, October 19, 1978; ID: 355.0011 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0011)
  - Interview with Stuart Sherman on four movies of his- Part one, October 19, 1978; ID: 355.0012 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0012)
    Original format: 1/4" audiocassette.
  - Interview with Stuart Sherman on his show. First and fifth tapes. Numbers 0-214 before first tape poetry readings. Tapes A and B., March 12, 1975; ID: 355.00013 (Box 28, Media ID: 355.00013)
    Original format: 1/4" audio reel
  - Interview with Stuart Sherman on his show 'Stuart Sherman makes a spectacle of himself'. Parts three and six. Numbers 17-20 Description plus interpretation Tape D. Numbers 13-17 Description plus interpretation Tape C., March 12, 1975; ID: 355.0014 (Box 28, Media ID: 355.0014)
  - Interview with Stuart Sherman on his show. Second and fourth tapes. Numbers 20-25, plus Numbers 1-2 Interpretation Tape E. Numbers 7-11 Descriptions, Numbers 12-13 Description plus interpretations Tape B., March 12, 1975; ID: 355.0015 (Box 28, Media ID: 355.0015)
  - Interview with Stuart Sherman on his show 'Stuart Sherman makes a Spectacle of himself'- Seventh tape. Numbers 8-11, interpretations then general questions. Tape G., undated; ID: 355.0016 (Box 28, Media ID: 355.0016)
  - Mel Andringa, September 6, 1977; ID: 355.0017 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0017)
  - Mel Andringa- The Last Supper, 1979; ID: 355.0018 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0018)
  - Mel Andringa- on August 'Catskills Camillo Workshop' and July New York Belshazzar, August 28, 1979; ID: 355.0019 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0019)
  - Mel Andringa, June 11, 1978; ID: 355.0020 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0020)
  - Mel Andringa on his recent trip to Iowa and then on Richard Foreman's "Hotel China", May 7, 1979; ID: 355.0021 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0021)
  - Mel Andringa- 136 West 81st Street- about New York City, Iowa, and Baltimore production, June 29, 1977; ID: 355.0022 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0022)
  - Mel Andringa- Lecture at Jaime Davidovich's, March 3, 1976; ID: 355.0023 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0023)
    From Series I: Performance Overview Subject Files A-Z Box 3 Folder 5: The Confidence Man [9 of 9] Material has accompanying envelope with quote
  - Mel Andringa- Artist Space lecture and Interview about Belshazzar's Feast given to Stefan Brecht by Mel Andringa with quote about Ashton and Coleridge, undated; ID: 355.0024 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0024)
  - Interview with Robert Whitman, February 7, 1976; ID: 355.0025 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0025)
    From Series I A-Z Robert Whitman [3 of 4]
  - Interview with Joan Evans, November 21, 1977; ID: 355.0026 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0026)
  - Shuji Terayama's "Directions to Servants" Music by J.A. Seazer performed by the Tenjosajiki Theatre Groupe Tokyo, Japan, undated; ID: 355.0027 (Box 27, Media ID: 355.0027)